# **Grant R Shurley**

#### **User Experience Strategist**

# **FCB** Chicago

#### **User Experience Strategist**

November 2017 - Present

Built a navigation map using qualitative and quantitative research and implemented it in a high-fidelity prototype for user testing for one of the top 5 health insurers.

Executed a atomic design strategy on an enterprise-level healthcare site.

Created detailed documentation for development teams on functionality and technology requirements of solutions.

Worked directly with planning, account, and creative teams to translate atomic design modules into high fidelity compositions using a content map.

Built user flows for various CRM programs and web forms that utilized user identified data to serve tailored content.

Designed a solution, which was approved by legal, to better use available screen real estate in regards to FDA mandated important safety information.

Met with development teams to walk through sprint demos, answer questions about website functionality, and provide front-end development solutions.

Consulted with other internal teams on the use of an agile workflow.

#### Colibri Group

#### **User Experience Designer**

August 2017 – November 2017

Worked with internal stakeholders to scope and create a common platform, based on atomic design principles, which all business arms could utilize both on front-end marketing sites, as well as, the backend proprietary software.

#### Codal

#### **User Experience Designer**

January 2017 – June 2017

Devised a solution to incorporate a company's corporate services into a single platform to increase overall assets obtained by the company.

Implemented a design sprint cycle to accomplish client goals by utilizing agile methodologies and the Google Ventures design sprint.

Adhered to client set deadlines to present design and architecture of a sports injury reporting platform to potential investors.

Orchestrated the mining of data from client database for use in discovery and research phases of a project.

**SKILLS** 

User Experience Design
System Architecture
Service Design
Digital Accessibility
User-Centered Design
Product Management
Project Management
Marketing Strategy
Client Relations
Information Technology
Creative Direction
Social Media Management

EDUCATION

# General Assembly

User Experience Design

# University of Missouri - Kansas City

# Missouri Southern State University

**TECHNOLOGY** 

Sketch

Axure

Invision

Photoshop

Illustrator HTML

**CSS** 

Agile

Data Visualization

**Analytics** 

Premiere Pro

After Effects

iOS

Android

ΙoΤ

SaaS

Digital Signage

Content Management Systems

Marketing Automation

Held weekly conference calls to mitigate potential setbacks and provide progress updates using compiled documentation and data from JIRA.

Developed project goals that addressed both user and business needs.

Presented ideas, findings, and designs to corporate executives, boards, or stakeholders on all projects.

Worked with client side customer service teams to identify end-user needs.

Designed a Mobile Device Management solution that limits child's screen time based on activity data collected from a connected fitness tracker.

#### **Appetize**

#### **Implementation Consultant**

September 2016 – December 2016

Organized and coordinated the implementation efforts at the Gaylord Family Oklahoma Memorial Stadium

Created a system to log iOS and Android based POS workstations and their IP configurations and locations.

Demonstrated to and trained client employees on using devices and software.

Solved critical in-game issues of workstations, wired/wireless network, printers, and credit card terminals.

#### **Freelance**

## **User Experience Designer & Strategist**

September 2015 – October 2016

Worked with a regional healthcare system to plan, design and project manage the development of a consumer-facing mobile application.

Strategized a multi-channel marketing campaign for a marathon.

Consolidated IT software and equipment to be more cost-effective and efficient for a digital signage business.

Consulted with an advertising agency on various inbound marketing practices.

#### Blu<sub>20</sub>

#### **User Experience Designer**

May 2014 – September 2015

Collaborated with multiple companies to strategize, wireframe, and design an inventory tracking application that utilized IoT technologies.

Planned, produced, and executed targeted regional retail marketing campaigns that generated over 500,000 impressions.

Produced a multi-award winning video campaign for a running and lifestyle company.

OTHER EXPERIENCE

#### **Art Feeds**

#### Intern

September 2013 – May 2014

#### **Zeus Visuals**

**Art Director & Web Manager** September 2013 – May 2014

#### **Joplin Schools**

EagleAlley, Founder &
Editor-in-Chief / Spyglass, Editor
September 2012 – May 2014

## Michael Shurley O.D., P.C

#### IT Manager

September 2010 – Present